# James Ciclitira

Product Designer based in London, creating complex digital products that lead to better user experiences. I love to design beautifully simple interfaces, code, iterate and create. I am an experienced and capable Digital Product Designer with over 2 years of professional experience.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Product & Web development

Suggestv · January 2017 - April 2017

Suggesty is the inventor of semantic video distribution. I was responsible for designing and aiding in the production of a semantic video distribution platform using React.

## Product designer

CrowdScores · September 2015 - January 2017

CrowdScores is a real-time sports data application. I had the pleasure of working as the principal designer taking responsibility for a variety of roles. Responsible included improving the existing product, developing new features research, conceptualising ideas & prototyping.

## Freelance designer

Prediction labs · January 2017 - Present

Numilli app - Bitcoin safe and easy. Numilli aims to makes it easy to securely buy and sell bitcoin currency, on the go using a mobile app & ATM machine.

## Freelance designer

Fireminds · March 2017 - Present

BaseSight - workforce management platform, which aims to help improve efficiency & productivity

### **EDUCATION**

The University of Edinburgh · 2011 - 2015 Product design - 2:1 ba (Hons)

#### **DESIGN SKILLS**

Sketching UI/UX Design Interaction Design Prototyping Grid & Layout Design Research Visual Design

#### DESIGN TOOLS





Illustrator

Photoshop

Invision

Pixate

## DEVELOPMENT

HTML

Javascript